我们快出发了吗
Are we gonna go soon?
我也不知道 宝贝 希望如此
I don't know, baby. I sure hope so.
我好饿
I'm hungry.
我明白 卡尔 大家都很饿
I know, Carl. We all are.
我去拿些吃的给他吧
Why don't I get him something to eat?
爱德对生存技能很有研究
Ed's into all this survival stuff.
我们的速食食品都够养活一个小型军队了
We've got enough m.R.E.S to feed a small army.
- 那谢谢了 - 没事
- I'd sure appreciate it. - No trouble.
你干嘛要告诉她这件事
What in the hell did you tell her that for?
我们根本就不认识这群人
We don't even know these damn people.
那个小男孩饿了 我们可以拿出一盒
That boy is hungry. We can spare one box.
这叫做 秘密行事
It's called operational security.
你他妈要是再这么乱发善心
How long do you think this stuff is gonna last.
这些东西很快就得被吃完
If you keep running your damn mouth off to everybody we meet?
对不起 我没多想
I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking.
找到什么了吗
You getting anything?
- 什么也没有 - 一点也不稀奇
- There's nothing. - Big surprise there.
不 我是说 什么都没有
No, I mean there's nothing.
紧急广播系统停了
Emergency broadcast system stopped,
还有播报难民安置中心消息的录音
and that recording about the refugee center.
都没了
It's all gone.
我往前走走 看能发现什么情况
I'm gonna go up the road, see what I can see.
我跟你一起去
I'll come with you.
爱德肯定是忘了把那些速食装包了
Ed must have forgot to pack those m.R.E.S.
- 我在我包里找到了这个 - 没事的
- I found these in my purse. - It's all right.
听着 你能帮我照看一会儿卡尔吗
Listen, do you mind keeping an eye on carl for a minute?
好的
No.
我和肖恩要去前面打探一下
Shane and I are gonna go scout up ahead a little bit.
看能不能找到了解情况的人
And see if we can find someone that knows what's going on.
- 我想和你们一起去 - 不行
- I want to come with you. - Huh-uh.
别担心 我们很快就会回来
Hey, we'll be back before you know it.
好吗 小男子汉
Okay, little man, huh?
他们为什么不播难民安置中心的消息了呢
Why would they stop broadcasting about the refugee center?
- 我也不知道 - 你觉得他们不再收人了吗
- I don't know. - Think they're turning people away?
如果真这样的话 肯定会引发动乱
They're gonna have a riot on their hands if they try.
- 你爸爸真好 - 肖恩不是我爸
- Your dad's nice. - Shane's not my dad.
我爸死了
My dad's dead.
- 我们该怎么办 - 过来
- What do we do? - Come here.
我们要做瑞克会希望我们做的
We're gonna do what rick would have wanted us to do,
带你和卡尔离开这里
Get you and carl out of here.
这可不是闪电
That's not lightning.
跟紧我 走吧
You stay with me now. Come on.
天啊
Oh my god.
他们在往街道上投汽油弹
They're dropping napalm in the streets.
肖恩
Shane.
到我这来
Come here.
《行尸走肉》
- 早啊 - 早上好
- Morning. - Good morning.
真不敢相信我居然睡过头了
I can't believe I slept in.
肯定是太困的缘故
You must have needed it.
感觉还好吧
Feeling all right?
下次要叫醒我 好吗
Next time wake me, all right?
特别是洗衣日
Especially on laundry day.
我能搞定的
I can manage.
我有个想法 想听听你的意见
I had an idea I wanted to run by you.
- 什么想法 - 他们家那个大厨房
- What's that? - That big kitchen of theirs got me thinking.
我挺想再在一个真正的厨房里做顿饭
I wouldn't mind cooking in a real kitchen again.
也许咱俩都能加入
Maybe we all pitch in.
今晚一起给赫谢尔和他的家人做顿晚餐
and cook dinner for hershel and his family tonight.
我只是找点事做 不让自己的脑袋闲着
Kind of looking for things to keep my mind occupied.
他们为我们付出了这么多
After everything they've done for us,
我们最起码也要这样
Seems like the least we could do.
介意我多邀请几个人吗
You mind extending the invitation?
我只是觉得经过你的同意比较好
Would just feel more right coming from you.
为什么这么想
How so?
你是瑞克的妻子
You're Rick's wife.
这或多或少让你成了我们的「第一夫人」吧
It sort of makes you our unofficial first lady.
大家早上好 我们开始行动吧
Morning, guys. Let's get going.
我们要找的地方有很多
We've got a lot of ground to cover.
好了 今天每个人都有新的搜寻区域
All right, everyone's getting new search grids today.
如果她能跑到
If she made it.
达里尔发现的那个农舍那么远的话
as far as the farmhouse daryl found,
也许她去了更往东点的地方
She might have gone further east than we've been so far.
我想帮忙
I'd like to help.
我对这片地方非常熟悉
I know the area pretty well and stuff.
赫谢尔同意吗
Hershel's okay with this?
是的 同意了 他说我该问问你
Yeah yeah. He said I should ask you.
那好 谢谢你
All right then. Thanks.
我不觉得达里尔的发现和索菲亚有关
Nothing about what Daryl found screams Sophia to me.
谁都可能躲在那个农舍里
Anyone could have been holed up in that farmhouse.
那也包括她 对吗
Anybody includes her, right?
睡在那个橱柜里的人
Whoever slept in that cupboard.
身高只有这么点儿
was no bigger than yay-high.
这是条好线索
It's a good lead.
也许我们该再沿着她的足迹找
Maybe we'll pick up her trail again.
别也许了 我要借匹马
No maybe about it. I'm gonna borrow a horse,
到那边的山脊去
head up to this ridge right here,
往这片地俯瞰一下
take a bird's-eye view of the whole grid.
如果她在那的话 我肯定能看到她
If she's up there, I'll spot her.
好主意
Good idea.
没准你还能看到个吸血怪兽呢
Maybe you'll see your chupacabra up there too.
- 吸血怪兽 - 你没听说过吗
- Chupacabra? - You never heard this?
我们住营地的第一天晚上
Our first night in camp,
达里尔说这让他想起有次去猎松鼠时
Daryl tells us that the whole thing reminds him.
看见了只吸血怪兽的事
of a time when he went squirrel hunting and he saw a chupacabra.
想怎么着 混蛋
What are you braying at, jackass?
这么说 你相信这世上有吸血狗存在
So you believe in a blood-sucking dog?
你相信死人能行走吗
Do you believe dead people walking around?
等等 你以前用过枪没
Hey hey. Ever fire one before?
如果我要出去的话 我得拿一个
Well, if I'm going out, I want one.
是吗 地狱里的人还想喝思乐冰呢
Yeah, and people in hell want slurpees.
明天你过来训练吧
Why don't you come train tomorrow?
如果你是认真的 我可是个持证教练哦
If you're serious, I'm a certified instructor.
现在他先跟着我们走
For now he can come with us.
那你负责做保姆看着他
He's yours to babysit then.
好了 安德莉亚 T仔 我要你们俩…
All right, Andrea, T-dog, I want you guys…
吉他不错
Nice guitar.
戴尔在高速上找到的
Dale found it on the highway.
知道吗 我们还有十一个避孕套
You know, we still have 11 condoms.
你看到的是十一个套套
You see 11 condoms,
我看到的是不堪回首的11分钟
I see 11 minutes of my life I'm never getting back.
没那么糟吧
It wasn't that bad, was it?
听着 我都不知道我是否喜欢你
Look, I don't even know if I like you.
但是你在思考这件事情
But you're thinking about it.
你是该考虑考虑
You should.
你还记得高中时 我们在DQ里遇到的
You remember the name of that waitress at the Dairy Queen.
那个女服务员的名字吗
when we were in high school?
我了解你 肖恩 我知道
I know you, Shane, well enough to know that there is only one.
要想让你开口聊天
sure-fire way of engaging you in a conversation,
就得先…
And that is to start.
问你在高中和女生们的风流史
asking you about girls you did in high school.
我也不想
I don't want to,
为了让你开口 逼不得已只能这样
but I'll willing to do it if that's what it takes.
玛丽安娜
Maryanne.
我跟你提过她吗
I told you about her?
说得很详细 简直是折磨人
In excruciating detail.
折磨人 去你的
Excruciating, my ass.
你以前就靠这些细节活着呢吧
You used to live for those details back in the day.
我那是近墨者黑
I was impressionable.
或许我一直身临其境地活在你的世界里呢
And I may have been living vicariously through you.
为什么不呢
Why wouldn't you,
感受着我那充满难忘成就的生活
with my impressive list of accomplishments?
我那时青春年少 精力旺盛
I was an artist in his prime.
- 孜孜学子 - 你是想说奇才吧
- A protege. - You mean prodigy.
或许吧
Maybe.
你把定期和三十岁的女人做爱的
Is prodigy what you call a young high school stud.
性感高中小男孩定义为「奇才」吗
that bangs 30-year-olds on the regular?
你在高中上了哪个三十岁的女人
What 30-year-old were you banging in high school?
- 体育老师 - 是丹尼尔斯先生吗
- The P.E. Teacher. - Mr. Daniels?
是凯莉夫人好吗
Mrs. Kelly.
女子排球的教练 她不是结过婚了吗
The girls volleyball coach? Wan't she married?
得了吧你
C'mon.
你猜我刚刚想到什么了
You know what I just remembered?
为什么我从没问过你这些事
Why I never ask you about this stuff.
怎么不说说你的高中恋爱史
Why don't we talk about your high school love life then, huh?
没什么事好说的
Well, that's a short conversation.
- 或许已经说完了 - 是吗
- It may even already be over. - That right?
有个叫霍莉的 对吧
There was Holly, right?
不对 那也是我搞的女人
Nope, that was me too.
有个叫希拉的 她的事你对我撒谎了
Then there was Sheila. That's the one you lied to me about.
我从没骗你有关希拉的事
I never lied about sheila.
我只是把「满垒」的意思理解错了
I just got mixed up about what the bases meant.
如你所知 「全垒打」通常是指性行为
Just so you know, a home run, that usually means a sexual act.
- 就是性交 - 我现在知道了
- That's intercourse. - Yeah, I realize that now.
我觉得你做的事
I think what you did was.
更像二垒打之类的
more like a ground rule double or something.
我现在知道裁定规则了
I'm aware of the judge's ruling.
不该谈这些的
Shouldn't be talking about this stuff.
曾经的生活 曾经的人 都不复存在
That life, it's gone and everyone in it.
希拉
Sheila.
玛丽安娜 凯莉夫人
Maryanne. Mrs. Kelly.
就好像我们已经老了
It's like we're old folk.
我们故事中的所有主人公都死了
All the people in our stories are all dead.
我们不能就这样忘了他们
We can't just forget them.
当然不行
The hell we can't.
不深掘过去 还得忘记所发生的事
It's hard enough accepting what's happened.
真的不容易
Without digging up the past.
我告诉你是什么吧
I'll tell you what it is.
是怀旧
It's nostalgia.
这就像嗑药
It's like a drug.
一直不让你看清真相
Keeps you from seeing things the way they are.
那玩意很危险 还有很多人依赖着你呢
That's a danger. You got people depending on you.
你以为我不知道这些吗
You think I don't know that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们这是在干什么
What are we doing?
你安排每个能派上用场的人
You got every able body at your disposal.
翻遍树林找一个
out scourging these woods.
你我心知肚明可能死了的小姑娘
for a little girl we both know is likely dead.
你觉得我们该停止搜索
You think we should abandon the search?
这事轮不到我来决定 对吧
It's not my call, is it?
我在征求你的意见 我在征求
I'm asking. I'm asking.
活下来是最重要 瑞克
Survival, Rick.
这就意味着要做出艰难的抉择
It means making hard decisions.
但你却有本事把我们越分越散
But you've got this knack. You spread us thinner and thinner.
我在努力救人
I'm trying to save lives here.
而你却忙着救树上的小猫
and you're out saving cats from trees.
你这么想吗 索菲亚就好比树上的猫
Is that what you think Sophia is, a cat in a tree?
别这样伙计 别歪曲我的本意
Don't do that, man. Don't twist my words.
有多少次我们被召集起来
How many times we get called up.
寻找失踪的孩子 哥们
to look for a missing child, man?
你只有黄金七十二小时 七十二小时
You got 72 hours. 72 hours, and after that.
那以后我们就是在找尸体了
You're looking for a body.
就连这都是很久以前的事了
And that was before.
你真指望我们找到索菲亚的时候
I mean you honestly think.
她还好好地活着吗
we're just gonna find sophia alive?
你确定不会吗
Are you that sure we won't?
要听实话是吧
We being completely honest?
我正指望你实话实说呢
I'm counting on you to be.
这是数学问题 伙计
It's math, man.
不管你喜不喜欢 索菲亚只有在
Love or not, Sophia, she only matters.
不拖累其他人的情况下才值得一救
to the degree in which she don't drag the rest of us down.
我还以为你想听实话呢
I thought you wanted honest.
如果当时我们继续前进
If we'd just moved on, man,
我们现在已经在去贝宁堡的路上了
we'd be halfway to Fort Benning.
卡尔更不会受枪伤
right now and Carl wouldn't have gotten shot.
你自己也这么说过
You said so yourself.
但我们还在野外寻找 冒着生命危险
But we're out here, we're risking lives.
你的亲生儿子差点因此送命
Your own son almost died.
奥蒂斯付出了生命的代价
Otis, he paid that bill.
我们在这里到底是为了什么
What the hell are we still doing this for?
我当时牵着她 肖恩
I had her in my hand, Shane.
她注视着我的双眼
She looked in my eyes.
信任我 我却让她失望了
And trusted me. I failed her.
如果不是这样 她根本不会逃亡在外
If I hadn't, she wouldn't be out here.
我相信她还活着 我不会…
I think she's still alive and I'm not…
我绝不会放弃她
I'm not gonna write her off.
蓝色的
It's blue.
是安德莉亚和T仔的
It's Andrea and T-dog.
看样子我们晃悠到他们的地盘了
Looks like we wandered into their grid.
索菲亚
Sophia!
悠着点 悠着点
Whoa. Easy easy.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
管好你自己的事 格伦
Mind your own business, Glenn.
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
别告诉任何人 求你了好吗
You can't tell anybody, okay?
你还没告诉他
You haven't told him yet?
出什么事了吗
Something wrong?
我和肖恩谈了很久
I just had a long talk with Shane.
他希望停止搜索
He wants to call off the search.
你怎么想的
What do you think?
如果出事的是卡尔怎么办
What if it was Carl?
你希望我们继续找他吗
Would you want us to keep looking?
如果是卡尔 不论如何我都想知道
If it was Carl, yes I'd want to know one way or another.
肖恩说我的好意
Shane says my good intentions.
会削弱我们的力量
are making us weaker,
还说我不能替队伍做出
that I can't make the hard decisions.
有利却艰难的决定
for the good of the group.
哪个决定不艰难
They're all hard decisions.
但我可能开始觉得
But maybe I'm holding on to a way of thinking.
那没有什么意义了
that doesn't make sense anymore.
他说这是数学题 最要紧的是活下来
He says it's math, basic survival…
还有多少燃料 多少食物 多少弹药
how much fuel, how much food, how much ammo.
那等式里容不下丁点软弱
Not much room in that equation for being soft.
当你这样看待生活的时候就容易多了
It's pretty simple when you start thinking of life like that.
听我说
Hey.
我们谁都没有准备好过这种生活
None of us were prepared to be living life this way.
你用已掌握的信息做了你能做的
You are making the best decisions you can.
最棒的决定 你一点都不软弱
with the information you have. I don't see soft in that.
格兰姆斯先生 我爸爸想和你谈谈
Mr. Grimes. My dad wants to talk to you.
你行的
Oh, come on.
你爬过一半了 别跟个娘们似的
You've done half. Stop being such a pussy.
加油
Come on.
我们少了一匹马
One of my horses is missing.
你的人动过吗
Did one of your people take it?
我以为你知道呢
I was given the impression you knew about that.
我并不知情
I did not.
我会和达里尔谈谈这事
I'll have a word with Daryl.
吉米呢
And Jimmy?
你今天带了他出去
You took him out today.
你也让你以为我同意了吗
Did he also give you the impression of my consent?
不 他直接说的 我信了他的话
No, he said it outright. I took the boy at his word.
吉米只有17岁
Jimmy is 17.
虽然他不是我家人 但我一样要负责任
He's not my kin but I am responsible for him.
这些事情都要先征得我的同意
These things need to be cleared with me.
看来我们得好好沟通一下
Sounds like we need to work on our communication.
你有什么建议
What do you suggest?
很简单
Keep it simple.
我管我的人 你管你的
I'll control my people, you control yours.
你为什么不把箭拔出来 笨蛋
Why don't you pull that arrow out, dummy?
那样就能把伤口好好包起来
You could bind your wound better.
莫尔
Merle.
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
你在午休吗
You taking a siesta or something?
今天走背运 老兄
A shitty day, bro.
要不要我给你拿个枕头来
Like me to get your pillow?
- 帮你挠挠脚 - 去死吧
- Maybe rub your feet? - Screw you.
看起来你才是快死的那个
Huh-uh. You're the one screwed from the looks of it.
我花了这么多年教你成为真正的男子汉
All them years I spent trying to make a man of you,
这就是结果吗 看看你
this is what I get? Look at you.
躺在泥里 像个用过的安全套
Lying in the dirt like a used rubber.
你会死在这的 老弟
You're gonna die out here, brother.
- 为了什么 - 一个小姑娘
- And for what? - A girl.
丢了个小姑娘
They lost a little girl.
你现在对小姑娘感兴趣了吗
So you got a thing for little girls now?
闭嘴
Shut up.
因为我发现你不再找老莫尔了
'cause I noticed you ain't out looking for old Merle no more.
我拼命地找过你 老哥
Tried like hell to find you, bro.
你才没有呢 你离开了
Like hell you did. You split, man.
一有机会你就自己走了
Lit out first chance you got.
离开的是你 当时你只要等下去就好
You lit out. All you had to do was wait.
我们回去找过你
We went back for you.
瑞克和我
Rick and I,
我们回去救你
We did right by you.
这和那个把我拷在屋顶上的瑞克
This the same Rick that.
是同一个人吗
cuffed me to the rooftop in the first place?
逼我不得不砍掉自己的手
Forced me to cut off my own hand?
我们说的是同一个人吗
This him we're talking about here?
你成他的小弟了吗
You his bitch now?
我不是谁的小弟
I ain't nobody's bitch.
你现在就是个笑话
You're a joke is what you are,
任这些娘娘腔 黑鬼和民主党人
playing errand boy to a bunch of.
差遣
pansy-asses, niggers and democrats.
对他们来说 你就是个怪胎
You're nothing but a freak to them.
乡巴佬
Redneck trash.
这就是你
That's all you are.
他们在背后取笑你
They're laughing at you behind your back.
你知道的 不是吗
You know that, don't you?
我告诉你 老弟
I got a little news for you, son.
总有一天 他们会把你蹬开
One day they gonna scrape you off their heels.
就好像你是一坨狗屎
like you was dogshit.
嘿
Hey.
他们不是你的亲人
They ain't your kin,
流着不一样的血
your blood.
你要是有点脑子
Hell, you had any damn nuts in that sack of yours,
就应该回去冲着瑞克来一箭 给我报仇
you'd got back there and shoot your pal Rick in the face for me.
听我说
Now you listen to me.
除了我 没人会在乎你 小弟弟
Ain't nobody ever gonna care about you except me, little brother.
没人会的
Nobody ever will.
快来 站起来
Come on, get up on your feet.
别等着我把你牙踢掉
before I have to kick your teeth in.
这个王八蛋说得对
Son of a bitch was right.
你可别成为鸟的腹中餐
Please, don't feed the birds.
怎么了 小达里尔
What's the matter, Darylina?
你就这点本事吗
That all you got in you?
把包扔掉 赶紧爬上来
Throw away that purse and climb.
你不在的时候我感觉比较好
I liked it better when you was missing.
得了吧 别这样
Come on, don't be like that.
我和你是一伙的
I'm on your side.
是吗 从什么时候开始
Yeah? Since when?
从你生出来开始 小弟弟
Hell, since the day you were born, baby brother.
虽然你没什么用 但总得有人照顾你
Somebody had to look after your worthless ass.
你从来没有照顾过我
You never took care of me.
你说的很好听 但从来没真做过
You talk a big game but you was never there.
你现在也一样不在 这些年来一直这样
Hell, you ain't here now. Guess some things never change.
我要告诉你的是
Well, I'll tell you what…
我和你的吸血怪兽一样真实
I'm as real as your chupacabra.
我清楚我看见了什么
I know what I saw.
我相信这和你吃的毒蘑菇
And I'm sure them shrooms.
没什么关系 对吧
you ate had nothing to do with it, right?
你最好闭嘴
You'd best shut the hell up.
要不然怎样
Or what?
你会上来帮我闭上嘴吗
You're gonna come up here and shut my mouth for me?
好吧 那快来做啊
Well, come on and do it then,
如果你够男人的话
if you think you're man enough.
快把你的高跟鞋踢掉 爬上来
Hey, kick off them damn high heels and climb, son.
你知道吗
You know what?
我要是你
If I were you.
就会停下来想想自己怎么会落到这般田地
I'd take a pause for the cause, brother.
因为我觉得你爬不上来
'cause I just don't think you're gonna make it to the top.
快来呀 快来 小弟弟
Come on. Come on, little brother.
抓住你朋友瑞克的手
Grab your friend Rick's hand.
你最好跑得远远的
Yeah, you'd better run.
是吗 我从没想过我见到土豆会这么高兴
Oh yeah? I never thought I'd be so happy to see a potato.
我只是很高兴
I'm just glad we're not.
我们不用用火堆烤松鼠了
roasting squirrels over a fire in the woods.
谢谢 帕特里夏
Thank you, patricia,
非常感谢你让我们进屋
so much for letting us into your house.
这是在干什么
What's this?
洛莉和卡萝尔今晚为我们做晚餐
Lori and Carol are cooking dinner for us all tonight.
没人告诉我这件事
That's the first I've heard of it.
我觉得这没什么关系
I didn't think it was that big a deal.
他们想要对我们的帮助表示感谢
They want to thank us for helping them.
我们应该和这些人划清界限
We need to be setting clear boundaries with these people.
他们过得有点太舒服了
They're getting a little too comfortable.
只是一顿晚餐
It's just dinner.
你和那个亚裔男孩怎么回事
What's going on with you and the Asian boy?
他叫格伦 我们是朋友
Glenn. He's a friend.
我更希望他和你没关系
I'd rather he wasn't.
我要管着贝丝和吉米就已经够糟糕的了
Bad enough I have to chase Beth and Jimmy around.
你不用管着我
Well, you don't have to chase me around.
我又不是16岁的小孩
I'm not 16.
我知道你不是
I know you're not.
所以我指望你能成熟点呢
That's why I'm counting on you to be the mature one.
你清楚我的感受
You know how I feel.
请不要让事情变得比原本更糟糕
Please don't make things harder than they need to be.
我已经长大了 你不用和我说这些
I'm a little old for us to be having this conversation.
不要和他们走得太近
Don't get close to them.
他们不会永远待下去的
They're not going to be around forever.
这位神枪手没事做了
What's with the Annie Oakley routine?
我不想再去洗衣服了 戴尔
I don't want to wash clothes anymore, Dale.
我想帮忙放哨
I want to help keep the camp safe.
有什么问题吗
Is that all right with you?
抱歉 我只是来还你的书
Sorry. Just returning your book.
不 我很抱歉
Oh no, I'm sorry.
早知道这是世界末日
If I had known the world was ending,
我就会带些更好看的书
I'd have brought better books.
戴尔 你说安德莉亚是不是到生理期了
Dale, you think andrea's on her period?
我这么问是因为好像所有女人
I'm only asking 'cause it's like all the women.
都举止怪异
Are acting really weird.
我在哪里看到过说女人如果
And I read somewhere that when women.
常常在一起 她们生理期会同步
spend a lot of time together, their cycles line up,
然后就同时荷尔蒙大爆发
and they all get super crazy hormonal at the same time.
我建议你
I'm gonna advise you.
这套理论自己知道就好
to keep that theory to yourself.
- 是啊 - 还有谁行为怪异了
- Yeah. - Who else is acting weird?
- 玛姬 - 啊 玛姬
- Maggie. - Ah, Maggie.
她一开始对我很刻薄
She started off being mean to me.
后来她想跟我嘿咻
Then she wanted to have sex with me.
现在又变得很刻薄
And now she's being mean to me again.
至于洛莉我都懒得问她
And I don't even want to know what's going on with Lori.
洛莉又怎么了
What's going on with Lori?
没什么 我不知道
Nothing. I don't know.
好吧 回到刚才那一句
All right, let's take this back a step.
你怎么知道玛姬想和你嘿咻
How do you know that Maggie wanted to have sex with you?
小伙子 你不是吧
Oh, son, you didn't.
你没想过她父亲会有什么反应吗
Did it ever occur to you how her father might feel about this?
她都22岁了
She's 22.
可是他是这里的主人
And he is our host.
他还不知道
He doesn't know.
是啊 看他会不会一直蒙在鼓里
Well, see that it stays that way.
天啊 格伦 你脑子秀逗了吧
Jesus, Glenn, what were you thinking?
我当时想
I was thinking.
可能明天我就挂了
That I might be dead tomorrow.
谢谢借书给我
Thanks for the book.
你说得对 这书超难看
You're right, it sucks.
行尸 行尸
Walker. Walker!
就一个吗
Just the one?
我打赌我可以从这里干掉它
I bet I can nail it from here.
别 安德莉亚 把枪放下
No no, Andrea. Put the gun down.
你最好让我们处理他
You'd best let us handle this.
肖恩 等等 让赫谢尔处理行尸
Shane, hold up. Hershel wants to deal with walkers.
为什么 老兄 我们能搞定
What for, man? We got it covered.
- 安德莉亚 不要 - 边儿去 戴尔
- Andrea, don't. - Back off, Dale.
那是达里尔吗
Is that Daryl?
这是你第三次拿枪指着我的头
That's the third time you've pointed that thing at my head.
你要开枪吗还是怎样
You gonna pull the trigger or what?
不
No!
瑞克
Rick!
到底发生了什么事
What on earth's going on out here?
- 我是开玩笑呢 - 起来
- I was kidding. - Come on.
我的天啊
Oh my god.
天啊 他死了吗
Oh my god, is he dead?
他昏过去了 子弹只是擦伤了他
Unconscious. You just grazed him.
但你看他 他到底发生什么事了
But look at him. What the hell happened?
他戴着耳朵项链
He's wearing ears.
别让他们看到就行
Let's keep that to ourselves.
兄弟们 这不是索菲亚的娃娃吗
Guys, isn't this Sophia's?
我在河床那里找到的
I found it washed up on the creek bed right there.
她一定是过河的时候弄掉的
She must have dropped it crossing there somewhere.
她差不多走了那片地儿的一半路程
Cuts the grid almost in half.
- 不用客气 - 他伤得怎么样
- Yeah, you're welcome. - How's he looking?
没想到抗生素会用得那么快
I had no idea we'd be going through the antibiotics so quickly.
你知道我的马去哪里了吗
Any idea what happened to my horse?
你说那匹差点要了我老命的马
Yeah, the one who almost killed me?
它要是有能耐 早另觅高枝了
If it's smart, it left the country.
我们叫它奈利 就是胆小鬼奈利的意思
We call that one Nelly, as in nervous Nelly.
如果你事先问我 我会告知你它会把你甩下
I could have told you she'd throw you if you'd bothered to ask.
你们这样莽撞还能活着真是奇迹
It's a wonder you people have survived this long.
他会没事的
He'll be all right.
虽然很难开口 但这次我同意赫谢尔
I hate to say it, but I'm with hershel on this one.
不能再这样出去了 特别是这次以后
Can't keep going out there, not after this.
你现在就想放弃？达里尔才冒着生命危险
You'd quit now? Daryl just risked his life.
带回来第一个确凿证据
to bring back the first hard evidence we've had.
你是这么看的
That is one way to look at it.
在我看来 达里尔今天为个娃娃差点送命
The way I see it, daryl almost died today for a doll.
对啊 我就知道你这么想
Yeah, I know how you see it.
我不是冷酷无情
I'm not out to be a hard case.
只是想现实一点
Just being realistic.
他得开始做这种艰难的抉择
He's just got to start making the tough calls.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right.
我也许并不赞同他所有做法
I may not agree with all of his choices,
但我尊重他的决定
But I respect him.
我知道你和我的选择
I know yours and mine.
你的选择并没那么难
And your way isn't harder.
世界上最容易的事
It's the easiest thing in the world.
就是撒手不去管别人死活
to cut our losses and to not help.
你一直告诉自己
You keep telling yourself you're.
在做艰难的抉择 其实你是想…
making the tough calls. You're really just trying…
现在这世上我唯一关心的就是你和卡尔
The only thing I care about now in this world is you and carl.
所以如果觉得我对别人视若无睹
So I apologize if I appear to be insensitive.
我道歉 但是你也看到
to the needs of others, but you see.
为了你俩的安全我愿意做任何事
I'll do whatever it takes to keep the two of you safe.
甚至是放弃一个迷路的孩子吗
Even abandoning a lost child?
- 真的吗 - 对
- Really? - Yeah.
我和我儿子不再是你的问题
My son and I are not your problem anymore,
或者借口了
Or your excuse.
- 他怎么样了 - 他会没事的
- How's he doing? - He'll be fine.
你呢
What about you?
我向达里尔开枪
I shot Daryl.
别太苛责自己
Don't be too hard on yourself.
我们都曾想向达里尔开枪
We've all wanted to shoot Daryl.
宝贝 我该怎么办
Baby, what do I do?
晚餐准备好了 你来吗
Dinner's ready. You coming?
- 需要帮助吗 - 不用 我马上来
- You need anything? - Huh-uh, I'll be right there.
谁会弹吉他
Does anybody know how to play guitar?
戴尔找到把不错的
Dale found a cool one.
应该有人会弹吧
Somebody's got to know how to play.
奥蒂斯会
Otis did.
是啊 他还弹得很好
Yes, and he was very good too.
（今晚 哪里见）
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
就是看起来的这样
As good as I look.
我带了晚餐给你 你一定饿坏了
I brought you some dinner. You must be starving.
小心 我缝了针
Watch out, I got stitches.
我想告诉你
You need to know something.
你今天为我女儿做的事
You did more for my little girl today.
比她父亲一生做的事都多
Than her own daddy ever did in his whole life.
换了瑞克和肖恩也会这么做的
I didn't do anything Rick or Shane wouldn't have done.
我知道
I know.
你和他们都是好人
You're every bit as good as them.
都是好人
Every bit.
（有试过在草棚里做吗）
你不该看到这个的
You weren't supposed to see this.